What’s been wrong with you since last night?
Act like you're heartbroken.
Don't feel down. It's not cool.
If Jean has someone else,
you can also have someone new.
Tee.
Hmm?
Have you ever kissed someone like this?
When will your class finish?
I’ll wait and go home with you.
I know. I’m going home now.
I thought we were gonna go home together.
It’s just going home together. Don’t make it a big deal.
I gotta go.
Boo!
Oh, aren't you surprised at all?
How did you get home yesterday?
You know what, the movie that we watched
was filmed nearby our school.
Tee.
Tee!
Tee, let's go.
Tee.
See you, Fuse.
Go.
What's wrong with him?
He's not even saying a word to me.
So arrogant.
Boo!
He's coming.
Frame, Est, what the hell are you doing?
Ugh.
Don't you think it's funny?
Stupid prank. Only a fool will believe it.
Wait and see who will believe it.
Boo!
Frame.
My soy milk.
Do you know who believe it now?
Your beloved friend, Wit,
believes it.
He's totally pranked.
My soy milk.
What?
That's none of my business.
You should clean it.
What?
What the hell are you doing?
We should clean it.
Okay.
Maybe clean it a bit.
Wait,
what will you use to clean it?
You used the mop for picking mangoes the other day.
I figured it out.
Use Wit's shirt.
Yeah.
Come here.
Take it off.
Take it off now.
You're the one who did it.
What's going on?
I didn't do that.
We don't have a mop.
Hey, I'll bring a mop for you.
From where? A mango tree?
Class 13.
Here.
Why does it have to be Class 13?
Tee.
Tee!
Fuse, what are you doing here?
I'm here to borrow a mop.
Sure, I'll get it for you.
That's fine.
Huh? Fuse!
I'm sorry, bro.
[Which class do you have next?]
Fuse, you aren't in this class. What brings you here?
Ah... yes.
Hey, you okay?
You should have told me you wanted to play table tennis.
Come on.
Look, the ball went too far, and Wit has to pick it.
Oh.
I didn't follow you.
I'm… I'm having lunch now.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Mo.
Hmm?
Can I pick your brain?
Go ahead.
Listen to me.
I'm listening.
Uh... it's not about me,
it's about my relative.
What's your relative's name?
Robert.
Surname?
Sae-tang.
Huh?
Robert Sae-tang.
You're relatives but have different surnames?
Mo.
I'm kidding.
Go ahead. What's going on with Robert Sae-tang?
Robert...
has a friend.
They're not close,
but he is a good friend.
And he helps Robert in many ways.
Uh-huh.
Come on.
You're so slow.
Come here.
Ugh.
Robert wanted to return him a favor,
so Robert waited to go home with him.
But something had come up,
so Robert had to leave first and...
Shit.
He's not shit.
Shit is shit.
Who's shit?
Robert Sae-tang.
Yeah, he's shit.
He's not.
He's shit.
He's not shit.
He's not.
Guys, stop.
Shit is a bad word.
If not,
I'll write your names down.
He said a bad word.
It's him.
It's him, teacher.
He said a bad word.
Write his name down.
Book, whose name did you write down?
Don't be nosy.
Hey, I'm asking you nicely.
Whose name did you write down? I'm curious.
Did it has my name?
It has nothing to do with you.
If you don't tell me,
I'll kiss you.
What did you say?
I'm asking you nicely.
If you don't tell me,
that means you want to kiss me.
Go wherever you want.
You said it yourself.
You said it, Book.
You said I can go wherever I want.
This is wherever I want.
It's not wrong to sit here, right?
Frame, go away.
My lips are soft. You can try them.
Book.
Hello.
What brings you here?
We're here to pick files for Teacher Banjong.
It's over there, I guess.
Have you done my homework yet?
Homework...
I've probably done it. I'll go back and get it done.
And you should come to school more often.
You've been absent too much.
Ah, I'll do it right.
Great.
I'm proud of you.
I'm here to pick up score sheets.
Score sheets?
Yes.
Okay.
Here you go.
Has your group finished the physics project yet?
That has to be submitted this evening.
Huh, this evening?
So you should hurry and get it done.
Go, or you won't finish it.
Okay.
Yessir.
You're giving me a headache.
Right,
I've something to show you.
What?
Wait a sec.
Um.
Hey.
[Are you Lookmo? I'm Tee from Class 13.]
[What's up?]
[Can I ask something about Fuse?
He has a girlfriend, right?]
[Why did you ask about that?]
[He acted strangely last night. I'm a bit worried.]
I don't know what's going on
between Tee and you.
But I think...
Tee seems to care a lot about you.
That's why I felt comfortable leaving you with him.
[Are you still with him?
Please take care of him. He's not doing well lately.]
Do you...
want to know
how to be like Tee?
You should try caring about others as he does.
Massage harder.
Hey.
Huh?
Why did you only give a massage to Frame?
Because I have only one hand.
You have two.
Come here.
Hurry up.
Fine.
Right,
do you think the class rep is pranking us?
How come we're the only ones
who don't know it has to be done today?
Yeah, I think so.
It's no surprise.
While studying,
none of us listened to the teachers.
Oh.
Why were you not listening?
Um.
I was talking with you.
Ugh.
You have to listen.
It's you who have to listen.
Yeah, it's you.
Why is it always me?
Tee!
Damn, that's sick!
Like a male lead in a series.
I bet...
you guys will definitely make up
within an hour.
Hey, what do you means by make up?
What's it?
Ask him.
Hey.
What's it?
What's it? Hey.
What?
Tell us.
Tee,
seriously,
are you mad at me?
I'm mad at you.
Be focus.
Focus.
I know.
I won't lose in this round.
Wait and see.
We'll win.
Hey, hey.
Hey, Mhek.
Go help me, there are a lot of customers now.
Nai, take this over.
What? Shit.
Whoa.
Your hands look so busy.
Oh.
Hello.
Whoa.
How about one more phone?
No, I can't handle them all.
Hey.
Hello, dad.
Hello.
Hi.
Are you guys here to play games?
Yes.
And I'm here for ice-cream as well.
Can I have my usual?
Okay.
I'll get Mhek bring it to you.
Thank you.
No problem.
Nai.
We're sorry.
We're working late today.
You guys are so late.
Nai, can I play with you?
Here, help me.
Hey, what about me?
Next round.
Boo, that's unfair.
Hey, focus on it.
I shot two of them already.
Hey, Frame.
Don't make it too obvious.
Are you watching a porn?
Nah.
Who's gonna watch it here?
I'm not Fuse.
That's a legend.
Hey, play properly.
[Is that a real-time pic?]
[I'm nearby.]
[Can I come over?]
[I'm still here, come over.]
-Shit!
-What?
I have to go.
Huh?
I'm leaving first.
Good luck.
Huh?
I gotta go.
See ya.
Keep playing.
Sorry.
Oh? What brings you here, class rep?
Hey.
Where are you going?
You're acting weird.
Are you here with your partner?
Let me go.
Hey.
You can tell me.
You're here with your partner?
Where's your partner?
Let me go.
Hey, you can tell me.
Where's your partner?
Ugh!
Don't tell me that you're BKBOii.
Sit here, there is no mosquito.
How's that possible?
Because I wave them away for you.
Tee.
I wish Batman were in Thailand.
Why?
So I would send him a signal to help us.
Tee.
Keep waving.
I think we can find a way out.
Let's go.
Huh?
We can get help without Batman.
Do you know an SOS signal?
Like this?
That's a hand signal.
I mean a light signal.
Turn on and off with a code like this.
Dot-dot-dot.
Dash-dash-dash.
Here, try it.
Dot-dot.
Dash. How did you do that?
Here.
I'll do it.
You have to do like this.
Dot-dot-dot.
Dash-dash-dash.
You wanna try?
Um.
Give it a try.
Dot.
Dot-dot.
Dash-dash-dash.
Dot-dot-dot.
Dash.
Dash-dash.
Dot-dot-dot.
Dash-dash-dash.
Fuse.
Hmm?
Look.
Hurry up.
Nadech.
Nadech, please open the door for us.
Ugh, these kids.
Ugh.
Jeez.
I have no words.
Here.
Aw. Thank you, Nadech.
How long have you been stuck in there?
Huh?
And why don't you use the intercom to call me?
He's Tee,
my school friend.
He'll sleep here tonight.
Class rep.
Are you really BKBOii?
You know what, this is crazy.
I do a hand job with your pics every night.
Hey.
You don't have to be embarrassed. It's normal.
I'm also a human.
Well,
your tattoo,
is it real?
Can I have a look?
If you let me have a look,
I'll let you go home.
I promise.
You promised.
Um.
Damn, it's real.
Can I touch it?
You promised me that you'll let me go home.
Hey, just once. Just once.
I promise. If you let me touch it, I'll let you go.
Damn, it looks so good.
Book.
I think...
I'm getting hard now.
Getting hard, my ass.
Well,
you wait for me here then.
I'll be right back to talk to you.
Wait for me.
Wait right here.
So satisfying.
If Fuse brings a handsome friend like this home,
will you be okay with him?
Of course.
But he have to be handsome
because I love handsome guys.
I'm just talking about what we watching.
By the way, people are much more open-minded now.
Whether we'll have a daughter-in-law or a son-in-law,
just let the kids decide.
I didn't say anything.
You didn't say anything?
That's cute, right?
Um. Thanks for walking me home.
And for helping me.
Help you what?
Huh?
Do you think I mean waving mosquitoes away?
I mean, about helping me get out of the building.
Without you,
I might be stuck until next morning.
How will you get home?
You should call a cab earlier.
Well... how about sleeping at my house?
Great.
Huh?
What about your uniform?
I already called a rider to pick up.
Did you set this up?
Hey.
You're thinking too much.
Let's get inside.
Pa, Ma.
Oh.
Hey, come here.
As agreed.
He's Tee, my school friend.
He'll sleep here tonight.
Here is my mom and dad.
Hello.
And that's Jie Fing.
My sister.
And Yaimai, her friend.
Hello.
Will you sleep here tonight?
I'll get the room ready for you.
Come here.
What?
Come and help me.
Can I sit here a bit longer?
I'm about to...
Have a seat.
Your friend is so handsome.
Seems like he comes from a series.
Um.
[Whether I kiss you or you kiss me,
it'll feel like kissing a log.]
Jie,
what did you show my parents?
Why? It's enjoyable.
It like a fantasy movie.
Enjoy,
but does not exist.
Hey.
Isn't it true?
How can a gay kiss a man
and not get punched in real life?
Huh?
Get punched?
But some of them don't punch.
If a friend kisses you,
won't you punch him?
There is no reason to punch friends.
Well...
do you kiss your friend?
What if that friend likes you?
Will you punch him?
Ugh.
Enough.
I'm out.
Do I have to go with you?
Hurry up.
Goodbye.
Can I really have this?
You can.
Jie won't find out.
Fuse!
There really is a man who
punched a gay man after he got kissed.
I saw it with my own eyes on Songkran.
But there are some of them who don't punch.
Um...
What if they don't punch
because they also like it?
No.
They just hate violence.
Why are you keep arguing?
Or...
did someone kiss you?
Go away.
Go packing your order.
Fuse.
You won't finish it in time then.
Go, go away.
That's too close.
Why? Can't I be close to you?
Fuse!
Gosh!
I didn't do it.
I didn't kiss.
I didn't lean on him.
I did nothing.
Oh.
Here.
Please leave me a product review,
Tee.
Sure.
Let's go. I want to do it too.
Please, hurry up.
I did it.
I leaned on him.
I kissed.
Tee.
Are you teasing me?
Come here.
[What if they don't punch]
[because they also like it?]
Like it?
Just beacuse I didn't punch means I like it?
[Signs of being in love]
[have both
noticeable shifts in mood and behavior.]
[For instance, you'll often
think about them with no reason.]
[Feel happy when you see them.]
[Your heart is beating fast or
being shy when you're near them.]
[Care about their feelings more than others.]
Often think about them.
Hey.
Tee.
Tee. Tee.
Feel happy.
Dot.
Dash.
Shit, heart is beating fast.
How am I supposed to know that?
It's normal.
Fuse.
Hey, why are you shirtless?
Huh? I don't have pajamas.
Have you done it?
Done what?
Homework.
I haven't done this chapter's yet.
Then, how about I do it for you?
Do what?
I mean homework.
If you want to do it, then do it.
But...
if you want to do it too, let me know.
What do you mean?
I mean homework.
Why the hell are you whispering?
Hey.
If not, your dad will be awake.
You do it. I'm gonna sleep.
Do you want to do it on the bed?
What's it this time?
Homework.
You're just messing around.
Hey, let me go.
Tee.
Hey.
Ugh.
Let me go.
I'm gonna sleep.
Get homework done.
Go.
Good night.
Good night, my ass.
Do homework.
My uniform is delivered.
I'll be right back.
Um.
Have...
a...
wet...
dream...
kub.
[Have a wet dream kub, class rep.]
[Fck.]
When did you get close to him?
Or are you gonna hit on Fuse?
Can I?
I'm Rodtang, Grade 10. I'm a fan of yours.
Didn't you get a tattoo to show people?
The reason why I get it
is none of your business.
Raise your hand if you're in love.
I'm so happy.
What about you?
Are you happy too?
Shall we try again?
I want to know that I...